A Guide to the Hugh L. Robertson Collection, 1948-1983
Virginia Room, Fairfax County Public Library
- Series 2: Photographs, 1948-1971
  - Sub-series 2-1: Fairfax County Fire Department, 1957-1971
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, group of unidentified officials posing inside, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, group of women posing by the cornerstone, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, guests enjoying refreshments, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, invocation prayer, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, invocation prayer, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, line in front of the refreshment table, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, minister shaking hands with firefighter, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, raising of the flag, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill cutting the ribbon, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill presenting Dewitt Crickenberger with service award at podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill shaking hands with firefighter, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill shaking hands with firefighter, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill speaking with two unidentified men, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, Rep. Joel Broyhill with Dewitt Crickenberger at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, two firefighters posing by the cornerstone, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, unidentified firefighter speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, unidentified firefighter speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, unidentified man speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, unidentified man speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, unidentified woman speaking at the podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of dignitaries, Dewitt Crickenberger, and podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of dignitaries, Rep. Joel Broyhill, and podium, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of seated crowd, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of seated crowd, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of seating area looking across Center Street, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - Vienna VFD Fire Station Dedication, view of seating area looking across Center Street, 1958 May 17 (Box 2, Folder 66)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - South Boston, Va., firefighters training on training tower, Undated (Box 2, Folder 67)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - South Boston, Va., group shot of Fairfax County participants of Annual Virginia State Fire School, 1960 August (Box 2, Folder 68)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - South Boston, Va., group shot of participants of Annual Virginia State Fire School, 1959 (Box 2, Folder 69)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - South Boston, Va., group shot of participants of Annual Virginia State Fire School, 1960 August (Box 2, Folder 70)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - South Boston, Va., group shot of participants of Annual Virginia State Fire School, Undated (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - Staunton, Va., group shot of participants of Staunton Fire School, 1962 July (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - Williamsburg, Va., fire truck pumping water from a stream, Undated (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - Williamsburg, Va., firefighters in gear, Undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - Williamsburg, Va., firefighters near a training building under a controlled burn, Undated (Box 2, Folder 75)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - Williamsburg, Va., firefighters posing on steps, Undated (Box 2, Folder 76)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - Williamsburg, Va., firefighters putting out a controlled burn, Undated (Box 2, Folder 77)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - Williamsburg, Va., firefighters training with hoses, Undated (Box 2, Folder 78)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - Williamsburg, Va., group shot of instructors of the Third Annual Virginia Firemen's School, 1958 June (Box 2, Folder 79)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - Williamsburg, Va., group shot of participants of the Third Annual Virginia Firemen's School, 1958 June (Box 2, Folder 80)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - Williamsburg, Va., training building, Undated (Box 2, Folder 81)
    - Virginia State Firemen's School - Williamsburg, Va., training tower, Undated (Box 2, Folder 82)
    - Williamsburg Fire Department, fire trucks in front of fire station, Undated (Box 2, Folder 83)
    - Willis H. Burton, Jr., portrait of Fairfax County's first Fire Marshall [4 photos], Undated (Box 2, Folder 84)
  - Sub-series 2-2: Crane Co., Undated
    - Crane Co. employee driving a forklift loading wall cabinet boxes onto boxcar, Undated (Box 2, Folder 85)
    - Crane Co. employee driving a forklift loading wall cabinet boxes onto boxcar, Undated (Box 2, Folder 86)
    - Crane Co. employee loading a boxcar, Undated (Box 2, Folder 87)
    - Crane Co. employee loading a boxcar, Undated (Box 2, Folder 88)
    - Crane Co. employee operating a forklift, Undated (Box 2, Folder 89)
    - Crane Co. employee operating a forklift, Undated (Box 2, Folder 90)
    - Crane Co. employee standing on ladder retrieving supplies, Undated (Box 2, Folder 91)
    - Crane Co. executives posing in front of Crane Co. sign, Undated (Box 2, Folder 92)
    - Crane Co. warehouse interior, Undated (Box 2, Folder 93)
    - Crane Co. warehouse interior, Undated (Box 2, Folder 94)
    - Crane Co. warehouse interior, Undated (Box 2, Folder 95)
  - Sub-series 2-3: Washington D.C., Maryland, and Virginia, 1948-c.1950s
    - Chapman's Mill/Beverley Mill, Broad Run, Va., Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Chrysler Dealership, car salesman handing a check to a couple (Washington D.C.?), Undated (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Chrysler Dealership, couple sitting in car holding up a check (Washington D.C.?), Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Church cornerstone ceremony, Archbishop Michael surrounded by crowd (Greek Orthodox Church of Saints Constantine and Helen?) [2 photos], c. 1950s (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Church cornerstone ceremony, Archbishop Michael surrounded by crowd (Greek Orthodox Church of Saints Constantine and Helen?), c. 1950s (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Franciscan Monastery of the Holy Land in America, Washington D.C., bishop holding chalice during mass, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Franciscan Monastery of the Holy Land in America, Washington D.C., clergy on the altar during mass, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Franciscan Monastery of the Holy Land in America, Washington D.C., clergy posing on the altar, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Franciscan Monastery of the Holy Land in America, Washington D.C., clergy sitting during mass, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Franciscan Monastery of the Holy Land in America, Washington D.C., elevated interior view of mass, Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Franciscan Monastery of the Holy Land in America, Washington D.C., unidentified Franciscan posing in front of the monastery [2 photos], Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Meridian Hill Park, Noyes Armillary Sphere and cascade fountain, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Old Barry Chapel cornerstone in St. Dominic Catholic Church, Washington D.C., Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Rock Creek Park, antique horse carriage, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Rock Creek Park, birdbath in a pond [6 photos], Undated (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Rock Creek Park, Boulder Bridge [3 photos], Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - Rock Creek Park, Hugh L. Robertson(?) posing on rocks with a camera, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Rock Creek Park, Rapids Bridge [4 photos], Undated (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Rock Creek Park, roadway to unknown bridge, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Rock Creek Park, Rock Creek, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Rock Creek Park, wagon wheel garden fountain [6 photos], Undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
    - Rock Creek Park, waterfall, Undated (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - Silver Spring, Maryland "Avenue of Progress" Celebration, ribbon cutting of Georgia Ave. underpass with Charles H. Kopeland, Gov. W. Preston Lane, and B&O Railroad President R.B. White [color negative], 1948 September 11 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Washington D.C., view from Arlington, Va. looking towards Lincoln Memorial and Arlington Memorial Bridge, Undated (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Sub-series 2-4: Embassy of Pakistan, Washington, D.C., c.1953-1955
    - Pakistan Ambassador Syed Amjad Ali and Begum Ali with actress Katharine Cornell at the National Theatre, c. 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Begum Ali dressing Capt. Azhar H. Sadik, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Begum Ali dressing Dr. Iffat Nafis Shoaib, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Begum Ali with Capt. Azhar H. Sadik, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Begum and Syed Amjad Ali with Capt. Azhar H. Sadik, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Capt. Azhar H. Sadik holding hands with unidentified woman, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Capt. Azhar H. Sadik shaking hands with father-in-law, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Capt. Azhar H. Sadik signing marriage contract, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Capt. Azhar H. Sadik speaking with unidentified man, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 33)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Capt. Azhar H. Sadik with unidentified man, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Dr. Iffat Nafis Shoaib signing marriage contract, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Dr.Iffat Nafis Shoaib, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Dr.Iffat Nafis Shoaib with father, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Mr. and Mrs. Azhar H. Sadik posing with their families, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Mr. and Mrs. Azhar H. Sadik, newlyweds, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Mr. and Mrs. Azhar H. Sadik, newlyweds sitting on couch, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 40)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, Syed Amjad Ali arriving, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 41)
    - Pakistan Embassy Wedding, unidentified individuals, 1954 May 6 (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Pakistan Embassy, Ambassador Syed Amjad Ali and Begum Ali shaking hands with woman, c. 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 43)
    - Pakistan Embassy, Ambassador Syed Amjad Ali with Vice President Richard Nixon and unidentified man, c. 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Pakistan Embassy, Richard Nixon and Pat Nixon with Ambassador Ali's daughter(?), c. 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Pakistan Embassy, Richard Nixon smoking a hookah, c. 1953-1955 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Prime Minister of Pakistan Visit, Begum Ali, Syed Amjad Ali, Begum Mohammed Ali, and PM Mohammad Ali Bogra arriving at Washington National Airport [2 photos], 1954 October 14 (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Prime Minister of Pakistan Visit, PM Mohammad Ali Bogra paging through newspaper clippings, 1954 October (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Prime Minister of Pakistan Visit, PM Mohammad Ali Bogra sitting on a desk, 1954 October (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Prime Minister of Pakistan Visit, Wreath Laying at the Tomb of the Unknowns, ceremonial units in front of Arlington Memorial Amphitheater, 1954 October 21 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Prime Minister of Pakistan Visit, Wreath Laying at the Tomb of the Unknowns, PM Mohammad Ali Bogra and officials on the steps of the Arlington Memorial Amphitheater, 1954 October 21 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Prime Minister of Pakistan Visit, PM Mohammad Ali Bogra and Syed Amjad Ali boarding airplane at Washington National Airport [2 photos], 1954 October 22 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Prime Minister of Pakistan Visit, PM Mohammad Ali Bogra walking with officials departing Washington National Airport, 1954 October 22 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Sub-series 2-5: Dumont Television Network Unknown Television Episode, c. 1950s
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, Dumont Television set showing live stream of program, Undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, host between two Indonesian women in the set kitchen, Undated (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, host posing with three Indonesian women on set, Undated (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, host standing with two Indonesian women at a table of cultural artifacts [2 copies], Undated (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, host with two Indonesian women in the set kitchen, Undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, Indonesian woman and host sitting on a couch [2 photos], Undated (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, Indonesian woman and host sitting on a couch, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, Indonesian woman dancing for the camera, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, Indonesian woman dancing for the camera, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, three individuals associated with the program(?), Undated (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, three Indonesian women off set [2 copies], Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, two Indonesian women showing host cultural artifacts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Dumont Television Network unknown program, two Indonesian women showing host cultural artifacts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Indonesian group of unidentified individuals, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Indonesian woman dancing for the crowd, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Indonesian woman dancing for the crowd, Undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Sub-series 2-6: Post-World War II Asia, 1947
    - Hugh L. Robertson and parents(?), 1947 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Hugh L. Robertson relatives (?) [5 photos], 1947 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Japan, children gathered in the street, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Japan, PMC locomotive in train yard, Undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - Japan, street scene, Undated (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Mount Fuji, Japan, aerial view of mountain, 1947 July (Box 4, Folder 16)
    - Qingdao, China, airplane graveyard, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Qingdao, China, aquarium, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Qingdao, China, children posing, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Qingdao, China, crowd congregating, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 20)
    - Qingdao, China, Edgewater Mansions Hotel, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Qingdao, China, field workers, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Qingdao, China, head of Pagoda Pier, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Qingdao, China, "Main Drag", 1947 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - Qingdao, China, Pagoda Pier, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Qingdao, China, Pagoda Pier, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - Qingdao, China, Pagoda Pier L to R: C.J. McGrath, George L. Marona, D.E. Wilson, and D.E. Lee, 1947 August (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - Qingdao, China, paifang gate, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 28)
    - Qingdao, China, Qingdao bus, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 29)
    - Qingdao, China, Qingdao Palace Temple, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 30)
    - Qingdao, China, Qingdao Palace Temple, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - Qingdao, China, Qingdao Palace Temple, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Qingdao, China, sampan boats, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Qingdao, China, sampan boats, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Qingdao, China, squadron office, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - Qingdao, China, U.S. warplane on Qingdao ramp, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Qingdao, China, view of a busy street, 1947 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Tokyo, Japan, bonsai trees in park garden, 1947 July (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Tokyo, Japan, city scene, 1947 July (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Tokyo, Japan, Japenese monument to World War I war dead, 1947 July (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Yokosuka, Japan, Japanese shrine, 1947 July (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Yokosuka, Japan, Japanese shrine, 1947 July (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Yokosuka, Japan, overturned Japanese ship, 1947 July (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Yokosuka, Japan, overturned Japanese ship, 1947 July (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Sub-series 2-7: Unidentified, Undated
    - Unidentified, ballroom social dance [4 photos], Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Unidentified, color portrait of a woman, Undated (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Unidentified, family portrait, Undated (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Unidentified, family posing in different rooms [5 photos], Undated (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - Unidentified, football game, referee watching receiver getting tackled, Undated (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Unidentified, house with "876" street number, Undated (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Unidentified, piano and string combo musicians posing, Undated (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Unidentified, portraits of brothers [8 photos], Undated (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Unidentified, portraits of unknown men [10 photos], Undated (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - Unidentified, portraits of unknown women [30 photos], Undated (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Unidentified, rear side view of a three-story house, Undated (Box 4, Folder 55)
    - Unidentified, view of farmland and distant hills, Undated (Box 4, Folder 56)
    - Unidentified, wedding [13 photos], Undated (Box 4, Folder 57)
    - Unidentified, wedding [4 photos], Undated (Box 4, Folder 58)
- Series 3, Negatives, 1948-1959
  - Sub-series 3-1: Fairfax County Fire Department, 1954-1959
    - Annandale VFD Fire Station, dispatchers office, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Annandale VFD Fire Station, dispatchers office, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Annandale VFD Fire Station, second floor social hall, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Annandale VFD Fire Station, second floor social hall, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Annandale VFD Fire Station, view of kitchen, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Annandale VFD Fire Station, view of kitchen through interior window, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Barn fire, firefighters fighting nighttime blaze, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Barn fire, firefighters fighting nighttime blaze, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Barn fire, Herndon VFD firefighters fighting flames, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Barn fire, nighttime view of barn in flames, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Barn fire, nighttime view of barn in flames, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Barn fire, nighttime view of barn in flames, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Barn fire, nighttime view of barn in flames, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Barn fire, nighttime view of barn in flames, Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - Barn fire, nighttime view of barn in flames [color negative], Undated (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Barn fire, tractor in barn consumed by flames, Undated (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Bill Spaulding, Vienna VFD, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Bill Spaulding, Vienna VFD, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Bill Spaulding, Vienna VFD, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Bill Spaulding, Vienna VFD, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - Bill Spaulding, Vienna VFD, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - Bill Spaulding, Vienna VFD, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - Bill Spaulding, Vienna VFD, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Bill Spaulding, Vienna VFD, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 24)
    - Bob Hunter, Vienna VFD captain, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Bob Hunter, Vienna VFD captain, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Bob Hunter, Vienna VFD captain, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Bob Hunter, Vienna VFD captain, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Bob Hunter, Vienna VFD captain, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - Bob Hunter, Vienna VFD captain, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Bob Hunter, Vienna VFD captain, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Bob Hunter, Vienna VFD captain, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Bob Hunter, Vienna VFD captain, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Bob Hunter, Vienna VFD captain, portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Car accident, idle car wreck in the middle of a busy Washington D.C. street, Undated (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Car accident, injured woman laying on the ground alongside overturned car in Washington D.C., Undated (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Car accident, injured woman laying on the ground in Washington D.C., Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Car accident, overturned car wreck in Washington D.C., Undated (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Car accident, pedestrians staring at overturned car wreck in Washington D.C., Undated (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Car accident, pedestrians walking by overturned car wreck in Washington D.C., Undated (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Car wreck, Ford F-100 crushed front, c. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Car wreck, Ford F-100 crushed interior of cab [2 negatives], c. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Car wreck, Ford F-100 overturned, c. 1954 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Car wreck, Mercury with a crushed roof parked in lot, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Car wreck, Mercury with a crushed roof parked in lot next to Nalls Garage (Falls Church, Va.) tow truck, c. 1956 (Box 5, Folder 45)
    - Central Fire Control Station KIF 337, five unidentified men at fire board, Undated (Box 5, Folder 46)
    - Central Fire Control Station KIF 337, five unidentified men at fire board, Undated (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Central Fire Control Station KIF 337, three unidentified men at fire board, Undated (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Central Fire Control Station KIF 337, three unidentified men at fire board, Undated (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Central Fire Control Station KIF 337, view of fire board, Undated (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Central Fire Control Station KIF 337, view of fire board, Undated (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Central Fire Control Station KIF 337, view of fire board, Undated (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Claude Shoop, Fairfax County Fire Department Dispatcher, Portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 53)
    - Claude Shoop, Fairfax County Fire Department Dispatcher, Portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - Claude Shoop, Fairfax County Fire Department Dispatcher, Portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Claude Shoop, Fairfax County Fire Department Dispatcher, Portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Claude Shoop, Fairfax County Fire Department Dispatcher, Portrait, Undated (Box 5, Folder 57)